ballerstatus.net 2008-06-12

# BallerStatus.com | Privacy Policy

|  |  |   
---  
  
We respect the privacy of our newsletter subscribers, customers, contacts, those who answer our surveys, and those who fill out our questionnaires. It is our policy: Choice and Consent: To respect the purpose for which our site visitors gave us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request.

**Third Party Use**

To not sell, rent, or loan our subscriber or customer lists to third parties for e-mail marketing. While we sell advertising in our e-mail publications to other companies, we never allow third parties any other use of these subscriber lists.

**Unsubscriptions**

To send our periodicals only to those who request them (that is, opt-in). We immediately unsubscribe those who request it through convenient unsubscribe links in every e-mailing. Our welcome message to subscribers and every issue of our newsletters/e-zine's clearly explain how to unsubscribe. We keep our subscription lists as clean as possible to prevent obsolete e-mail addresses which use unnecessary bandwidth.

**Cookies**

To use cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors, not snoop on them. We use cookies to: (a) to help rotate banner advertising; (b) to identify shoppers with their shopping carts; (c) to make it easy to order a second time; (d) to allow subscribers to store passwords in cookies if they desire; and (e) to give proper credit for sales made through links on our affiliates' sites. We do not collect or use information from cookies to develop a profile about our visitors or shoppers.

**Security**

To store subscriber and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or off-line.

**Termination**

To continue this policy beyond the termination of our company. If a majority portion of the assets of our company were to be acquired by another organization, that might include our subscriber and other lists, but only as part of a clear agreement binding that organization to abide by the spirit and letter of our privacy policy.

If you have any concerns or questions about our privacy policy or information collected on our sites, please contact us at info@ballerstatus.com  
  
  |  |   
---  
|  |  |  |  |   
---  
|   |  News  
Young Jeezy Launches Social Networking Site  
Young Jeezy took a leap into the online trend on Wednesday (June 11) with the launch of USDA2Day.com, a new blog & ... full story  
---|---  
 |  Features  
Sean 'The Pen' Garrett: Blessed With A Gift  
If you found yourself in '04 belting out the lyrics to Ursher's "Yeah" in the club, holding back those "Goodies" like ... full story  
 |  Editorials & Columns  
Crisis Of The N**** Intellectual: How Conscious Hip-Hop Failed Us  
Here comes MC Revolutionary X, dressed down in his military gear with a Malcolm X t-shirt, raising his black fist, vowing ... full story  
 |  Beyond Hip-Hop  
Kevin Garnett Lands 'NBA 2K9' Cover  
2K Sports recently announced that that 11-time NBA All-Star and 2008 Defensive Player of the Year, Kevin Garnett, has ... full story  
 |  Reviews  
Devin The Dude: _Smoke Sessions Vol. 1_  
Perhaps not since Necro's Death Rap has an album been named more appropriately than Devin the Dude's new street album/mixtape, ... full story  
 |  Video  
Some Questions With Gritz: Dizzee Rascal  
In the first episode of "Some Questions with Gritz," resident blogger and writer, Gritz, sits down with UK grime sensation ... full story
